<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: celta | The Life and Times of AJ]]></title>
  <link href="http://ajdyka.github.com/blog/categories/celta/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ajdyka.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-02-01T22:02:24+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://ajdyka.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[AJ Dyka]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[aj.dyka@warpax.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back Online]]></title>
    <link href="http://ajdyka.github.com/blog/2012/08/07/back-online/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-07T18:26:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://ajdyka.github.com/blog/2012/08/07/back-online</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The haitus has been a bit longer than I anticipated, but a lot has happened!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The CELTA course took a lot more out of me than I anticipated, in face it left basically me no time to do anything that wasn't course related for the 4 weeks that it ran.</p>

<p>After the course finished I spent two weeks catching up with family and friends back home in Victoria before flying out to Hong Kong.</p>

<p>Since I landed here it's been a matter of acclimatisation both to the weather and the lifestyle :) I think I've settled in pretty well … while I haven't made any new friends as such I've been becomming familiar with the area that we live in (Ma On Shan, New Territories) and applying for a bunch of jobs, both IT and NET (Native English Teaching).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The start of a new beginning]]></title>
    <link href="http://ajdyka.github.com/blog/2012/04/15/the-start-of-a-new-beginning/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-15T21:30:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://ajdyka.github.com/blog/2012/04/15/the-start-of-a-new-beginning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tomorrow I begin a four week course, "Cambridge ESOL Certificate in English Language Teaching to Adults (<a href="http://www.cambridgeesol.org/exams/celta/index.html">CELTA</a>)" at <a href="http://www.attc.edu.au/">ATTC</a>.</p>

<p>By all reports it's pretty full on, 9-5:30 weekdays with homework every night as well as some weekend prep time being required. I sure won't be bored!</p>

<p>This is a bit of a deviation from my existing career in CFML web development, and there's a good reason for that!</p>

<!--MORE-->


<p>As probably already know, Tasmin and I are <a href="/about/">moving to Hong Kong</a>, in fact she is already there getting our new appartment ready while I finish things off in Sydney.</p>

<p>This has meant that I have started looking for work in HK already, and honestly it's been pretty difficult finding any CFML being used there at all (which somewhat surprised me!).</p>

<p>I've been doing the obligitory Google searches, researching and hitting up local job hunting sites and even contacted a few recruitment agents to no avail.</p>

<p>At this point rather than 'putting all of my eggs in one basket', I thought it would be an appropriate time to enhance some of my other skills and get CELTA certified. (I already posess a Certificate IV in Assessment and Workplace Training and a TEFL Certificate)</p>

<p>I'm still optimistic that I can pick up some remote consultancy work so I can maintain my CFML skills. In the event I cannot find anything permenant, I'll have the CELTA qualificaiton to fall back on either in the capacity of classroom teacher or private tutor.</p>

<p>Over the coming weeks I'll post details on my progress through the course, keep an eye on the category:<a href="/blog/categories/celta/">celta</a> for all related posts!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
